{
  "title": "Response Test",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "When do you have to pick John up at the airport? ........",
      "answers": [
        "He flew into the international airport",
        "I don't think she's coming",
        "I should be there at about five o'clock"
      ],
      "correct": "I should be there at about five o'clock"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "What are you going to buy your wife for Christmas? ........",
      "answers": [
        "I picked it up yesterday",
        "A bottle of perfume",
        "She received jewelry from her mother"
      ],
      "correct": "A bottle of perfume"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "How many people are coming to the birthday party? ........",
      "answers": [
        "There were about 70 people at the restaurant around the corner",
        "Fifty people were there",
        "We're expecting about 25 people"
      ],
      "correct": "We're expecting about 25 people"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "What are you doing tonight? ........",
      "answers": [
        "We had a great time",
        "I went to that new Asian restaurant",
        "I think I'm going to a movie with Susan"
      ],
      "correct": "I think I'm going to a movie with Susan"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "How was your honeymoon? ........",
      "answers": ["It was great", "We went by plane", "We went to Mexico"],
      "correct": "It was great"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "What is your favorite kind of food? ........",
      "answers": [
        "I ate Mexican food yesterday",
        "I like Italian food",
        "Korean cuisine is very spicy"
      ],
      "correct": "I like Italian food"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Who is coming to the business conference? ........",
      "answers": [
        "The management team and the personnel department are coming for sure",
        "The assembly line workers were there",
        "Fifty members attended the conference"
      ],
      "correct": "The management team and the personnel department are coming for sure"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "What are your thoughts on yesterday's meeting? ........",
      "answers": [
        "I think the president will be there",
        "I'm glad we covered the human resources' issue",
        "We should bring up the workers' concerns"
      ],
      "correct": "I'm glad we covered the human resources' issue"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "When are you going to the party? ........",
      "answers": [
        "We're going right after work",
        "We arrived at 7 pm",
        "Cindy is coming with me"
      ],
      "correct": "We're going right after work"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Where is the best place to go for a drink? ........",
      "answers": [
        "La Cantina has some great food",
        "I'll meet you there after work",
        "The little pub around the corner has great beer on tap"
      ],
      "correct": "The little pub around the corner has great beer on tap"
    }
  ]
}
